Mayank Raj

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

agrmayank@outlook.com

7544864618

linkedin.com/in/agrmayank

https://agrmayank.com

Summary

Experienced XR Developer and Co-Founder of Amnesea, specializing in creating immersive XR experiences.

Notable achievements include presenting 'KeyBound' and 'TimeBound' at IGDC 2023 with overwhelmingly positive feedback, a MadeWithUnity showcase selection and speaker at Unity Day, Pune. Also, a Top 10 Finalist in BYOG Game Jam by IGDC 2023.

At Nextech3D.Al & ARway, developed the ARway & ARwayKit SDK, an all-in-one metaverse creation studio for spatial mapping in immersive experiences. Crafted 'HARMONY,' a London-based mini-metaverse with AR artwork compositions. Founder of AgrMayank Studios, recognized for popular AR apps and games with 100k+ downloads.

Proficient in Unity3D, C#, C++, Python, and Flutter. Holds a Bachelor's in Information Technology, complemented by certifications in Machine Learning and Handheld AR App Development.

Experience



🞇 Co-Founder

Amnesea

Jul 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

- Presented 'KeyBound' and 'TimeBound' at India Game Developers Conference (IGDC), receiving an overwhelmingly positive response from the attendees, investors and publishers.
- "TimeBound: History's Legacy" was chosen as a Top 10 finalist in the BYOG game jam by IGDC.

Number

Nextech3D.AI

Sep 2021 - Present (2 years 4 months)

- Acquired ARway in September 2021, which later became a spinoff in October 2022.
- Developed ARway & ARwayKit SDK a complete solution for powering camera devices with Augmented Reality & AI to recognize their surroundings for hyper-accurate location apps.

Founder

AgrMayank Studios

Jun 2020 - Present (3 years 7 months)

- Launched popular AR apps like Planets AR gaining 100k+ downloads on Google Play, etc alongside the development of immersive XR games like Spacey's Adventures for JioGlass.
- Led teams for the design and development of acclaimed PC, Mac and Web games with Unity, showcasing a talent for building unique and entertaining gaming experiences.
- Google Play https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=8444157410268700876
- · Itch.io https://agrmayank.itch.io



🛕 AR Developer

ARway.ai - The Spatial Computing Platform

Aug 2020 - Present (3 years 5 months)

- Developed ARway an all-in-one metaverse creation studio that enables users to create immersive experiences by spatially mapping their location.
- Developed HARMONY, a mini-metaverse in London that features AR artwork compositions from students at Guildhall School of Music & Drama and the London Symphony Orchestra.

Unity VR Developer

Round Them Oranges

Jan 2021 - May 2021 (5 months)

• Built Virtual Segments - a digital web gallery that showcases diverse artworks from around the world in an immersive and engaging way keeping engagement with art alive during the COVID-19 lockdown.

AR Developer

North Shore Therapeutics

Aug 2020 - Aug 2020 (1 month)

- Developed NST-SSD: Therapeutic Augmented Reality for Schizophrenia to cure the negative symptoms of schizophrenia that obstruct reward circuitry in the brain.
- The aim is to help the patients "build belief in self capacity" by activating the reward circuitry.



Senior AR Developer

Noora Health

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020 (3 months)

 Developed "Virus Warrior" – a coronavirus shooting game in AR – and "PPE Trainer" – an AR nurse training app for the Donning/Doffing procedures of the COVID-19 equipment - for Noora Health.

Education



Trident Academy of Technology (TAT), Bhubaneswar

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology

2016 - 2020

- Managed a team to build a spider-bot project using 3D printing and IoT devices with Augmented Reality at the CISCO thingQbator incubator within college premises.
- Launched an e-commerce website using WordPress, Amazon Affiliate, GoDaddy, etc.
- Involved in over 5 workshops & sessions by Cisco thingQbator, NASSCOM Foundation & Li2 Technologies in a span of 3 months.
- · Actively participated in multiple GDG (Google Developer Group) Bhubaneswar sessions and Engaged in AR VR and Blockchain Workshops @KIIT E-Summit 2018.



Delhi Public School, Ranchi

12th Board (Senior Secondary), Computer Science

2014 - 2016

Managed a cutting-edge technology-focused website/blog using a custom domain and hosting.

Licenses & Certifications

Machine Learning by Andrew NG (Stanford) - Coursera SQ3CG73VQ2BC

Handheld AR App Development with Unity - Coursera
UCA7QXRMBJH8

Skills

Augmented Reality (AR) • Game Development • Unity3D • Machine Learning • Flutter • Python • C# • C++ • Blockchain • Entrepreneurship

Honors & Awards

- 40 F: U

Top 10 Finalist in the BYOG Game Jam by IGDC - India Game Developer

Conference

Nov 2023

• Led the design and development of "TimeBound: History's Legacy" which was chosen as a Top 10 finalist in the BYOG game jam by IGDC.

Speaker & MWU showcase at Unity Day, Pune - Unity

Aug 2019

• Selected as a speaker for my game prototype "Foggy Forest", one of the only 9 Made With Unity (MWC) showcases at Unity Day, Pune.